Guide to the UE Organizers Records, 1937-2003 UE.7.3
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Organizer Records, 7-3-1.
  - Dunbar, Rosalyn, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Duncan, Robert, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Dunikowski, Katherine, 1943-1944 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Dunks, Judy, 1946-1947 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Dunman, Paul, 1941-1947 (Box 13, Folder 50-52)
  - Duplisea, Brian: Correspondence, 1992-1999 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Duplisea, Brian: Organizer Reports, 1992-1999 (Box 13, Folder 54-55)
  - Durbin, Manuel: Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Durbin, Manuel: Miscellaneous, 1986-1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Durbin, Manuel: Organizer Reports, 1985-1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Dutner, Fred, 1946-1953 (Box 14, Folder 03-04)
  - Dwyer, Francis, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Dwyer, Thomas, 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 06-07)
  - Easling, Howard, 1946-1947 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Ecker, Lee, 1944-1946 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Eckland, Donald, 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Eckstein, Bertrum, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Eddy, Mary, 1942-1943 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Eisenberg, Julie: Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Eisenberg, Julie: Organizer Reports, 1994-1996 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Eisenscher, Michael: Correspondence, 1972-1984 (Box 14, Folder 15-16)
  - Eisenscher, Michael: Organizer Reports, 1975-1983 (Box 14, Folder 17-19)
  - Elconin, William, 1940s (Box 14, Folder 20-29)
  - Elk, Gene, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Ellett, Thomas: Correspondence, 1993-1999 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Ellett, Thomas: Organizer Reports, 1993-1999 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Ellingwood, Harry, 1937-1948 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Ellis, Robin, 2000-2002 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Emens, John, 1942-1947 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Emerine, Robert, 1946-1948 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Encelewski, Morris, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Ennis, Francis, 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Evans, Barbara: Correspondence, 1985-1993 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Evans, Barbara: Organizer Reports, 1985-1989 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Evans, Barbara: Organizer Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Eveleth, Keith: Correspondence, 1989-1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Eveleth, Keith: Organizer Reports, 1990-1999 (Box 15, Folder 03-04)
  - Fagerhaugh, Harold, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Fagerhaugh, Ole, 1941-1942 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Falley, Sam, 1942-1943 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Farga, Rolando, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Fasanella, Ralph, 1942-1946 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Faver, William, 1945-1949 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Fernandes, John: Correspondence, 1993-1998 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Fernandes, John: Organizer Reports, 1993-1998 (Box 15, Folder 12-13)
  - Ferritto, Patricia, 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Field, Elizabeth, 1942-1945 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Fiering, Clara: Correspondence, 1947-1967 (Box 15, Folder 16-21)
  - Fiering, Clara: Organizer Reports, 1948-1964 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Fiering, Henry, 1939-1947 (Box 15, Folder 23-35)
  - Fiering, Henry, 1939-1947 (Box 16, Folder 01-08)
  - Fink, Carlton, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Fisher, Lisa, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Fisher, Roberta, 1944-1945 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Fishman, Harry, 1946-1947 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Fitzgerald, Daniel, 1945-1948 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Fitzpatrick, Thomas, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Flaherty, Charles, 1942-1944 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Flaherty, Jack, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Flanagan, Thomas, 1941-1945 (Box 16, Folder 17-19)
  - Flynn, Helen, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Foley, Robert, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Foley, Thomas, 1942-1944 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Foscue, Kenneth, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Foulk, George, 1939-1948 (Box 16, Folder 24-26)
  - Fox, Ruth, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Francis, Gail: Correspondence, 1997-2001 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Francis, Gail: Organizer Reports, 1997-2001 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Frantz, Margaret, 1944-1947 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Frazier, James, 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 31-32)
  - Frazier, William, 1946-1947 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Fredendall, Lloyd, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Freeman, William, 1944-1945 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Freitas, William, 1966-1969 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - French, Peter: Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - French, Peter: Organizer Reports, 1987-1991 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Fridy, Charles, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Fried, Emmanuel, 1943-1947 (Box 16, Folder 40-42)
  - Fuhrman, Michael, 1988-1990 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Gadsden, Reuben: Correspondence, 1978-1988 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Gadsden, Reuben: Organizer Reports, 1978-1988 (Box 16, Folder 45-46)
  - Gallagher, Robert, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Gallagher, Seth, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Garcia, Fred, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Garcia, Reuben, 1988-1991 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Garcia, Robert: Organizer Reports, 1975-1983 (Box 17, Folder 04-05)
  - Garcia, Robert: Correspondence, 1975-1986 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Garcia, Sandra, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Garfield, Arthur, 1937-1943 (Box 17, Folder 08-33)
  - Garner, Ella Mae, 1942-1945 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Garner, Joseph, 1941-1942 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Garrett, William, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Garza, Ellen, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Gaspar, Manuel: Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Gaspar, Manuel: Organizer Reports, 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Gaspar, Manuel: Discrimination Case Against the UE, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Gathers, Carnell: Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Gathers, Carnell: Organizer Reports, 1985-1988 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - George, Al, 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Gerald, Florence, 1944-1946 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Giermanski (Dunikowski), Katherine, 1943-1947 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Gifford, Robert: Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Gifford, Robert: Organizer Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Gilbert, William, 1937-1940 (Box 18, Folder 03-04)
  - Gill, George, 1937-1938 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Giuliani, David, 1945-1948 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Giunta, Mia: Correspondence, 1976-1984 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Giunta, Mia: Organizer Reports, 1977-1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Given, Claud, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Gojack, John, 1940-1942 (Box 18, Folder 10-12)
  - Goldberg, Samuel, 1942-1947 (Box 18, Folder 13-14)
  - Goldstein, Esther, 1942-1945 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Goldstein, Jack, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Gordnier, Lyle, 1943-1947 (Box 18, Folder 17-18)
  - Gordon, Basil, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Gould, Oscar, 1946-1947 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Grabbe, Stanley, 1943-1945 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Grayson, Raymond, 1943-1945 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Green, James, 1946-1947 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Greenseid, Maxwell, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Greenwood, Ryan, 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Grieshober, William, 1946-1947 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Griffing, Michael: Correspondence, 1986-1991 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Griffing, Michael: Organizer Reports, 1986-1991 (Box 18, Folder 28-29)
  - Grina, Leif, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Grote, Leon: Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Grote, Leon: Organizer Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Gruber, Sam, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Gutierrez, Rodolfo, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Guzman, Orlando, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Gyler, Emanuel, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Hafter, Harry, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Hagstrom, Eric, 1937, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Hall, Everard, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Hallem, Sharon, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Haller, Al, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Hamilton, Kenneth, 1963-1981 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Hammer, Edith, 1941-1945 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Hanson, Christopher, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Harley, Hugh, 1939-1970 (Box 18, Folder 45-55)
  - Harley, Hugh, 1939-1970 (Box 19, Folder 01-04)
  - Harris, Don, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Harris, Fred, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Harris, Joseph, ca.1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Harris (LeBlanc), Shirley, 1946-1947 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Harrison, Robert, 1944 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Hart, James: Correspondence, 1963-1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Hart, James: Organizer Reports, 1963-1981 (Box 19, Folder 10-12)
  - Hartmann, Richard: Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Hartmann, Richard: Organizer Report, 1996-1998 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Haug, Fred, 1941-1945 (Box 19, Folder 15-17)
  - Haurbleu, N., 1943-1944 (Box 19, Folder 18-19)
  - Heagy, Donald: Organizer Reports, 1983-1986 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Hein, August, 1936-1937 (Box 19, Folder 21-23)
  - Henderson, Violet, 1944 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Henry, Lee, 1942-1943 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Henson, Louise, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Herron, Jimmy, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Herzog, Florence, 1942-1949 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Heverly, Norman, 1943-1946 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Higgins, Lowell, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - High, Charlotte, 1942-1944 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Hill, Jennifer, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Hinds, Steve: Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Hinds, Steve: Organizer Reports, 1995-1998 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Hines, Edward, 1944-1947 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Hirschberg, Herbert, 1943-1947 (Box 19, Folder 36-46)
  - Hitzfelder, John, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Hoag, Alvan, 1945-1946 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Hoag, Diantha, 1943-1947 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Hochman, Steven: Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Hochman, Steven: Organizer Reports, 1980-1984 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Hoel, Betty, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Hoff, Ray, 1936-1937 (Box 20, Folder 02-04)
  - Holden, William: Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Holden, William: Organizer Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Hollenbach, Louis, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Holmes, John (Jack): Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Holmes, John (Jack): Organizer Reports, 1951-1986 (Box 20, Folder 09-15)
  - Hood, Joe, 1941-1945 (Box 20, Folder 16-18)
  - Horie, Jean, 1943-1945 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Horowitz, Maurice, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Hourihan, Martin, 1939-1944 (Box 20, Folder 21-25)
  - Houseman, Joseph, 1948-1959 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Hovedskou, Janet, 1942-1944 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Hovis, John: Correspondence, 1972-1979 (Box 20, Folder 28-29)
  - Hovis, John: Organizer Reports, 1942-1984 (Box 21, Folder 01-05)
  - Howard, Harry, 1938-1940 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Hrubee, James, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Humphrys, Lydia, 1942-1943 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Hull (Buczek), Katerine, 1942-1947 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Igoe, Carol, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Infante, Joseph, 1942-1947 (Box 21, Folder 11-13)
  - Iria, Nomesia, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Jackson, Clarence, 1937-1941 (Box 21, Folder 15-21)
  - Jackson, Daniel, 1945-1946 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Jacobson, Laurence, 1941-1947 (Box 21, Folder 23-26)
  - James, Helen, 1944-1945 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Janes, Erma, 1942-1943 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Jarvis, Ginny: Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Jarvis, Ginny: Organizer Reports, 1984-1987 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Jeep, Vincent, 1944-1945 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Jefferson, Malvice, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Jenkofski, William, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Jimenez, Michael, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 34-35)
  - Joel, Louis, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Johnson, David: Correspondence, 1983-1998 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Johnson, David: Organizer Reports, 1981-1991 (Box 21, Folder 38-39)
  - Johnson, David: Organizer Reports, 1991-1998 (Box 22, Folder 01-02)
  - Johnson, Henry, 1942-1945 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Jonas, Frank, 1985-1988 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Jones, Roberta, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Jones, Thurlow, 1940-1942 (Box 22, Folder 06-07)
  - Jorgens, Darrow: Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Jorgens, Darrow: Organizer Reports, 1985-1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Jorgenson, Lief, 1937-1938 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Kallish, Robert: Correspondence, 1979-1984 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Kallish, Robert: Organizer Reports, 1979-1984 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Kanes, David, 1943-1945 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Kaplan, Harry, 1941-1969 (Box 22, Folder 14-15)
  - Kaplan, Louis, 1946-1948 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Karsch, Doris, 1942-1943 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Karson, John, 1943-1945 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Katzen, Leon, 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Kazell, Michael, 1944-1946 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Keefe, Angela, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Keesey, Truman, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Keihl, Earl, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Keller, Charles: Correspondence, 1957-1968 (Box 22, Folder 24-25)
  - Keller, Charles: Organizer Reports, 1960-1969 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Keller, Fred, 1944-1949 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Kelly, Maude, 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Kelly, Thomas, 1949-1953 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Kelly, Shavonna, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Kennedy, Vernon, 1937-1939 (Box 22, Folder 31-33)
  - Kerns, Charles, 1953-1955 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Kerstein, Morris, 1947-1950 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Kessler, George, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Kidd, David, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Killinger, Charles, 1949-1952 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Kimball, Beatrice, 1949-1952 (Box 22, Folder 39-40)
  - Kimmel, Louis, 1941-1956 (Box 22, Folder 41-42)
  - King, Charlotte: Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - King, Charlotte: Organizer Reports, 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - King, Rosemary, 1948-1954 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Kingsbury, Douglas: Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Kingsbury, Douglas: Organizer Reports, 1965-1968 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Kinsella, Marjorie: Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Kinsella, Marjorie: Organizer Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Kinsey, Lloyd, 1944-1948 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Kirkendall, K.M., 1937-1949 (Box 23, Folder 08-10)
  - Kirkland, Thomas, 1957-1963 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Kirkwood, Robert: Correspondence, 1939-1948 (Box 23, Folder 12-18)
  - Kirkwood, Robert: International Representative, 1972-1976 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Kirsch, Howard, 1941-1943 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Kitto, Russell, 1944-1947 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Kline, Leonard, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Klinefelter, Letha, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Klipple, Jodi, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Knopf, Vernal, 1946-1947 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Knowles, Mary, 1943-1944 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Knowlton, Peter: Correspondence, 1985-2001 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Knowlton, Peter: Organizer Reports, 1986-2000 (Box 23, Folder 28-29)
  - Koedinger, Earl: Correspondence, 1967-1981 (Box 23, Folder 30-31)
  - Koedinger, Earl: Organizer Reports, 1967-1981 (Box 24, Folder 01-03)
  - Kogy, Al, 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Korman, Albert, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Korman, Paul, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Kosik, Frank, 1946-1947 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Kotelchuck, David, 1980-1984 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Koth, Robert, 1979-1984 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Koth, Robert, 1979-1985 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Kozar, Mike, 1940-1948 (Box 24, Folder 11-12)
  - Kozier, Sam, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Kozik, Frank, 1948-1950 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Kozma, William, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Kramer, Hilda, 1943-1946 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Krane, Irving, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Kraus, Eugene, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Krause, Roberta: Correspondence, 1988-2000 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Krause, Roberta: Organizer Reports, 1988-2000 (Box 24, Folder 20-21)
  - Krehbiel, Paul: Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Krehbiel, Paul: Organizer Reports, 1986-1989 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Kreisberg, Ben, 1944-1948 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Kres, Joseph, 1939-1941 (Box 24, Folder 25-29)
  - Kronstadt, Samuel, 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Krumm, Wilford: Correspondence, 1951-1962 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Krumm, Wilford: Organizer Reports, 1951-1961 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Kruth, Neils, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Kuehnel, William, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Kugelmass, Lois: Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Kugelmass, Lois: Organizer Reports, 1974-1980 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Kushner, Sam, 1944-1946 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Kuzio, Stephen, 1955-1957 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Kyler, Robert, 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - LaDassor, Gray, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Lafore, Tenaya, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Lambert, Samuel, 1945-1946 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Lamm, David, 1983-1988 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Lancaster, Debra, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Landa, Freedom, 1942-1944 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Landy, Edward, 1941-1956 (Box 25, Folder 09-11)
  - Lang, Harvey, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Lara, Francisco, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Laskowski, Kathleen: Correspondence, 1976-1983 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Laskowski, Kathleen: Organizer Reports, 1976-1982 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Laughlin, Helen, 1945-1946 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Lavanderos, Jose, 1988-1991 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Lavins, Edward, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Lawson, Charles, 1949-1955 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Lawson, Judith: Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Lawson, Judith: Organizer Reports, 1986-1989 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - LeBlanc, Adrian, 1945-1954 (Box 25, Folder 22-23)
  - Ledsome, William: Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Ledsome, William: Organizer Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Lee, Anna, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Lee, Margaret, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Lee, Paul, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Lee, Ray, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Lehane, William, 1943-1944 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Leith, Alex, 1951-1956 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Lennon, John, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Lesser, Martin: Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Lesser, Martin: Organizer Reports, 1976-1978 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Levie, Elizabeth: Correspondence, 1988-1994 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Levie, Elizabeth: Organizer Reports, 1988-1993 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Levitt, Mac, 1942-1945 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Levy, Mark: Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Levy, Mark: Organizer Reports, 1975-1981 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Lewin, Leonard, 1941-1946 (Box 25, Folder 40-42)
  - Lewis, Doris, 1942-1946 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Lewis, Hugh, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Lewis, Michael, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Linsley, Richard, 1939-1955 (Box 26, Folder 01-15)
  - Lipschultz, Lawrence, 1978-1984 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Lissitz, Sam, 1939-1940 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Litell, Charles, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Little, Sharon, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Livingston, Frederick, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Lockwood, James, 1944-1947 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Lodico, Paul: Correspondence, 1978-1992 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Lodico, Paul: Organizer Reports, 1978-1992 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Logsdon, Robert: Correspondence, 1939-1955 (Box 26, Folder 24-38)
  - Logsdon, Robert: Correspondence, 1948-1955 (Box 27, Folder 01-07)
  - Logsdon, Robert: Organizer Reports, 1948-1955 (Box 27, Folder 08-09)
  - Losada, Fernando: Correspondence, 1996-2001 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Losada, Fernando: Organizer Reports, 1996-2001 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Lovely, Joseph, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Lovett, Lillis, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Lowell, Charles, 1977-1986 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Loza, Efran, 1981-1984 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Lugo, Jose: Correspondence, 1962-1982 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Lugo, Jose: Organizer Reports, 1963-1975 (Box 27, Folder 17-18)
  - Lusk, U.S., 1937 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Lustig, James, 1937-1939 (Box 27, Folder 20-21)
  - Lutz, Lloyd, 1945, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 22-23)
  - MacDonald, George, 1942-1946 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Mackesy, William, 1942-1943 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - MacWhinnie, Angela, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Magalon, Dolores, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Majors, T. Louis, 1942-1951 (Box 27, Folder 28-35)
  - Malloy, Tom, 1937-1939 (Box 27, Folder 36-39)
  - Mamber, Phillip: Correspondence, 1975-1990 (Box 27, Folder 40-41)
  - Mamber, Phillip: Organizer Reports, 1975-1990 (Box 28, Folder 01-02)
  - Mance, Frank, 1942-1943 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Mancusa, Mary, 1942-1943 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Manning, Richard, 1965-1966 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Marcus, Ralph, 1941-1950 (Box 28, Folder 06-08)
  - Marfia, Frank, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Margolin, Joseph, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Marhanka, Richard, 1949-1950 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Marino, James, 1944-1954 (Box 28, Folder 12-14)
  - Markland, Lemuel, 1944-1946 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Markley, Alex: Correspondence, 1969-1985 (Box 28, Folder 16-17)
  - Markley, Alex: Organizer Reports, 1969-1985 (Box 28, Folder 18-21)
  - Markley, Alex: Legal Bills, 1976-1979 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Markley, Alex: Conspiracy Charges, 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 23-24)
  - Marsh, F.R., 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Marsh, James, 1944-1948 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Marsh, Jennifer, 2000-2002 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Martin, David: Correspondence, 1978-1984 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Martin, David: Organizer Reports, 1978-1983 (Box 28, Folder 29-32)
  - Martin, Ernest, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Martinez, Ana Yolanda: Correspondence, 1988-1993 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Martinez, Ana Yolanda: Organizer Reports, 1988-1993 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Martinson, H.M., 1947-1948 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Marty, Joseph, 1946-1947 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Marvin, Fay, 1946-1949 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Maschoff, Otto, 1941-1955 (Box 29, Folder 05-08)
  - Massa, Leon, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Massie, Roger, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Massman, Richard, 1968-1971 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Mates, David, 1943-1956 (Box 29, Folder 12-15)
  - Matison, Matthew, 1941-1945 (Box 29, Folder 16-17)
  - Matlis, Eben, 1946-1947 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Matthews, Edward, 1941-1944 (Box 29, Folder 19-21)
  - May, Alfred, 1954-1955 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - May, James, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Mayville, Harry, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - McAvoy, Clifford, 1947-1953 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - McBain, Francis, 1946-1947 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - McBride, Judith Ann, 1990-1994 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - McCabe, Francis, 1949-1950 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - McCaffrey, John, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - McCale, Lonnie, 1944-1948 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - McCann, Joseph, 1946-1956 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - McCarthy, John, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - McCarthy, Nelson, 1944-1945 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - McCartney, Margaret, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - McClellan, Richard, 1943-1946 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - McClure, Robert, 1937-1938 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - McConnell, William, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - McCool, Leo, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - McCormick, Cornelius, 1943-1947 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - McDonald, Charles, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - McDonough, Bernard, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - McDonough, John, 1941-1951 (Box 29, Folder 42-43)
  - McGarrey, Andy, 1944-1947 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - McGill, Harry, 1949-1950 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - McGill, John, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - McGillicuddy, Neale, 1940-1948 (Box 29, Folder 47-48)
  - McGinn, Mary: Correspondence, 1996-2003 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - McGinn, Mary: Organizer Reports, 1996-2002 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - McGlothin, Grant, 1942-1943 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - McGrew, Earl, 1936-1939 (Box 29, Folder 52-63)
  - McGuire, John, 1942-1943 (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - McIntyre, Hugh, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - McKinley, Edward, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - McLaughlin, John, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - McLellon, Richard, 1943-1944 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - McNair, Wilber, 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - McNamara, Catherine, 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - McPherson, Albert, 1944-1948 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Mejia-Moreno, Alberto, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Melchin, Alfred, 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Meyer, Rachel: Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 30, Folder 9)